<?xml version="1.0" encoding="US-ASCII"?>
<!DOCTYPE rfc SYSTEM "rfc2629.dtd" [
        <!ENTITY RFC2119 SYSTEM "http://xml.resource.org/public/rfc/bibxml/reference.RFC.2119.xml">
        <!ENTITY IANA_PEER_TYPE_LOC_RIB "TBD">
        <!ENTITY IANA_PEER_UP_INFO_TLV_TABLE_NAME "TBD">
        ]>

<?xml-stylesheet type='text/xsl' href='rfc2629.xslt' ?>
<?rfc strict="yes" ?>
<?rfc toc="yes"?>
<?rfc tocdepth="4"?>
<?rfc symrefs="yes"?>
<?rfc sortrefs="yes" ?>
<?rfc compact="yes" ?>
<?rfc subcompact="no" ?>

<rfc category="std" docName="draft-ietf-grow-bmp-local-rib-00"
     ipr="trust200902" submissionType="IETF"
     updates="7854">

    <front>
        <title abbrev="BMP Local-RIB">
            Support for Local RIB in BGP Monitoring Protocol (BMP)</title>

        <author fullname="Tim Evens" initials="T" surname="Evens">
            <organization>Cisco Systems</organization>

            <address>

                <postal>
                    <street>2901 Third Avenue, Suite 600</street>
                    <city>Seattle</city>
                    <region>WA</region>
                    <code>98121</code>
                    <country>USA</country>
                </postal>

                <email>tievens@cisco.com</email>

            </address>
        </author>

        <author fullname="Serpil Bayraktar" initials="S" surname="Bayraktar">
            <organization>Cisco Systems</organization>

            <address>

                <postal>
                    <street>3700 Cisco Way</street>
                    <city>San Jose</city>
                    <region>CA</region>
                    <code>95134</code>
                    <country>USA</country>
                </postal>

                <email>serpil@cisco.com</email>

            </address>
        </author>

        <author fullname="Manish Bhardwaj" initials="M" surname="Bhardwaj">
            <organization>Cisco Systems</organization>

            <address>

                <postal>
                    <street>3700 Cisco Way</street>
                    <city>San Jose</city>
                    <region>CA</region>
                    <code>95134</code>
                    <country>USA</country>
                </postal>

                <email>manbhard@cisco.com</email>

            </address>
        </author>

        <author fullname="Paolo Lucente" initials="P" surname="Lucente">
            <organization>NTT Communications</organization>

            <address>

                <postal>
                    <street>Siriusdreef 70-72</street>
                    <city>Hoofddorp</city>
                    <code>2132</code>
                    <region>WT</region>
                    <country>NL</country>
                </postal>

                <email>paolo@ntt.net</email>

            </address>
        </author>

        <date year="2017"/>

        <area>General</area>

        <workgroup>Global Routing Operations</workgroup>
        <keyword>BGP</keyword>
        <keyword>BMP</keyword>
        <keyword>local-rib</keyword>
        <keyword>loc-rib</keyword>

        <abstract>
            <t>
                The BGP Monitoring Protocol (BMP) defines access to the Adj-RIB-In
                and locally originated routes (e.g. routes distributed into BGP from
                protocols such as static) but not access to the BGP instance Loc-RIB.
                This document updates the BGP Monitoring Protocol (BMP) RFC 7854 by
                adding access to the BGP instance Local-RIB, as defined in RFC 4271
                the routes that have been selected by the local BGP speaker's
                Decision Process. These are the routes over all peers, locally
                originated, and after best-path selection.
            </t>
        </abstract>
    </front>

    <middle>
        <section title="Introduction" anchor="Introduction">
            <t>
                The BGP Monitoring Protocol (BMP) suggests that locally originated
                routes are locally sourced routes, such as redistributed or otherwise
                added routes to the BGP instance by the local router. It does not
                specify routes that are in the BGP instance Loc-RIB, such as routes
                after best-path selection.
            </t>
            <t>
                <xref target="FigAdjRibInLocRib"/> shows the flow of received routes from one or more BGP peers
                into the Loc-RIB.
            </t>

            <figure align="center" anchor="FigAdjRibInLocRib"
                    title="BGP peering Adj-RIBs-In into Loc-RIB">
                <artwork align="center"><![CDATA[
    +------------------+      +------------------+
    | Peer-A           |      | Peer-B           |
/-- |                  | ---- |                  | --\
|   | Adj-RIB-In (Pre) |      | Adj-RIB-In (Pre) |   |
|   +------------------+      +------------------+   |
|                 |                         |        |
| Filters/Policy -|         Filters/Policy -|        |
|                 V                         V        |
|   +------------------       +------------------+   |
|   | Adj-RIB-In (Post)|      | Adj-RIB-In (Post)|   |
|   +------------------       +------------------+   |
|                |                          |        |
|      Selected -|                Selected -|        |
|                V                          V        |
|    +-----------------------------------------+     |
|    |                 Loc-RIB                 |     |
|    +-----------------------------------------+     |
|                                                    |
| ROUTER/BGP Instance                                |
\----------------------------------------------------/
]]></artwork>
            </figure>

            <t>
                As shown in <xref target="FigLocallyOriginated"></xref>, Locally originated follows a similar flow where
                the redistributed or otherwise originated routes get installed into
                the Loc-RIB based on the decision process selection.
            </t>

            <figure align="center" anchor="FigLocallyOriginated"
                    title="Locally Originated into Loc-RIB">
                <artwork align="center"><![CDATA[
/--------------------------------------------------------\
|                                                        |
| +----------+  +----------+  +----------+  +----------+ |
| |  IS-IS   |  |   OSPF   |  |  Static  |  |    BGP   | |
| +----------+  +----------+  +----------+  +----------+ |
|       |            |             |              |      |
|       |                                         |      |
|       |  Redistributed or originated into BGP   |      |
|       |                                         |      |
|       |            |             |              |      |
|       V            V             V              V      |
|    +----------------------------------------------+    |
|    |                 Loc-RIB                      |    |
|    +----------------------------------------------+    |
|                                                        |
| ROUTER/BGP Instance                                    |
\--------------------------------------------------------/
]]></artwork>
            </figure>

            <t>
                BGP instance Loc-RIB usually provides a similar, if not exact,
                forwarding information base (FIB) view of the routes from BGP that
                the router will use. The following are some use-cases for Loc-RIB
                access:
            </t>

            <t>
                <list style="symbols">
                    <t>
                        Adj-RIBs-In Post-Policy may still contain hundreds of thousands
                        of routes per-peer but only a handful are selected and
                        installed in the Loc-RIB as part of the best-path selection.
                        Some monitoring applications, such as ones that need only to
                        correlate flow records to Loc-RIB entries, only need to collect
                        and monitor the routes that are actually selected and used.

                        <vspace blankLines="1"/>

                        Requiring the applications to collect all Adj-RIB-In Post-Policy
                        data forces the applications to receive a potentially
                        large unwanted data set and to perform the BGP decision process
                        selection, which includes having access to the IGP next-hop
                        metrics. While it is possible to obtain the IGP topology
                        information using BGP-LS, it requires the application to
                        implement SPF and possibly CSPF based on additional policies.
                        This is overly complex for such a simple application that only
                        needed to have access to the Loc-RIB.
                    </t>
                    <t>
                        It is common to see frequent changes over many BGP peers, but
                        those changes do not always result in the router's Loc-RIB
                        changing. The change in the Loc-RIB can have a direct impact
                        on the forwarding state. It can greatly reduce time to
                        troubleshoot and resolve issues if operators had the history of
                        Loc-RIB changes. For example, a performance issue might have
                        been seen for only a duration of 5 minutes. Post
                        troubleshooting this issue without Loc-RIB history hides any
                        decision based routing changes that might have happened during
                        those five minutes.
                    </t>
                    <t>
                        Operators may wish to validate the impact of policies applied
                        to Adj-RIB-In by analyzing the final decision made by the
                        router when installing into the Loc-RIB. For example, in order
                        to validate if multi-path prefixes are installed as expected
                        for all advertising peers, the Adj-RIB-In Post-Policy and Loc-RIB
                        needs to be compared. This is only possible if the Loc-RIB
                        is available. Monitoring the Adj-RIB-In for this router from
                        another router to derive the Loc-RIB is likely to not show same
                        installed prefixes. For example, the received Adj-RIB-In will
                        be different if add-paths is not enabled or if maximum number
                        of equal paths are different from Loc-RIB to routes
                        advertised.
                    </t>
                </list>
            </t>

            <t>
                This document adds Loc-RIB to the BGP Monitoring Protocol and
                replaces <xref target="RFC7854">Section 8.2</xref> Locally Originated Routes.
            </t>

            <section title="Current Method to Monitor Loc-RIB">
                <t>
                    Loc-RIB is used to build Adj-RIB-Out when advertising routes to a
                    peer. It is therefore possible to derive the Loc-RIB of a router by
                    monitoring the Adj-RIB-In Pre-Policy from another router. While it
                    is possible to derive the Loc-RIB, it is also error prone and
                    complex.

                    <vspace blankLines="1"/>

                <figure align="center" anchor="FigCurLocRibMon"
                        title="Current method to monitor Loc-RIB">
                    <artwork align="center"><![CDATA[
/------------------------------------------------------\
|  ROUTER1 BGP Instance                                |
|                                                      |
|     +--------------------------------------------+   |
|     |                 Loc-RIB                    |   |
|     +--------------------------------------------+   |
|                    |                    |            |
|    +------------------+     +------------------+     |
|    |   Peer-ROUTER2   |     |   Peer-ROUTER3   |     |
|    | Adj-RIB-Out (Pre)|     | Adj-RIB-Out (Pre)|     |
|    +------------------+     +------------------+     |
|    Filters/Policy -|    Filters/Policy -|            |
|                    V                    V            |
|   +-------------------+     +-------------------+    |
|   | Adj-RIB-Out (Post)|     | Adj-RIB-Out (Post)|    |
|   +-------------------+     +-------------------+    |
|              |                          |            |
\------------- | ------------------------ | -----------/
          BGP  |                     BGP  |
          Peer |                     Peer |
   +------------------+          +------------------+
   |   Peer-ROUTER1   |          |   Peer-ROUTER1   |
/--|                  |--\    /--|                  | --\
|  | Adj-RIB-In (Pre) |  |    |  | Adj-RIB-In (Pre) |   |
|  +------------------+  |    |  +------------------+   |
|                        |    |                         |
| ROUTER2/BGP Instance   |    | ROUTER3/BGP Instance    |
\------------------------/    \-------------------------/
            |                              |
            v                              v
    ROUTER2 BMP Feed               ROUTER3 BMP Feed
]]></artwork>
                </figure>

                    <vspace blankLines="2"/>

                    The setup needed to monitor the Loc-RIB of a router requires another
                    router with a peering session to the target router that is to be
                    monitored. As shown in <xref target="FigCurLocRibMon"/>, the
                    target router Loc-RIB is advertised via Adj-RIB-Out
                    to the BMP router over a standard BGP peering session. The BMP
                    router then forwards Adj-RIB-In Pre-Policy to the BMP receiver.
                </t>

                <t>
                    The current method introduces the need for additional resources:

                    <list style="symbols">
                        <t>
                            Requires at least two routers when only one router was to be
                            monitored.
                        </t>
                        <t>
                            Requires additional BGP peering to collect the received updates
                            when peering may have not even been required in the first
                            place. For example, VRF's with no peers, redistributed bgp-ls
                            with no peers, segment routing egress peer engineering where no
                            peers have link-state address family enabled.
                        </t>
                    </list>
                </t>

                <t>
                    Complexities introduced with current method in order to derive
                    (e.g. correlate) peer to router Loc-RIB:

                    <list style="symbols">
                        <t>
                            Adj-RIB-Out received as Adj-RIB-In from another router may have
                            a policy applied that filters, generates aggregates, suppresses
                            more specifics, manipulates attributes, or filters routes. Not
                            only does this invalidate the Loc-RIB view, it adds complexity
                            when multiple BMP routers may have peering sessions to the same
                            router. The BMP receiver user is left with the erroneous task of
                            identifying which peering session is the best representative of
                            the Loc-RIB.
                        </t>
                        <t>
                            BGP peering is designed to work between administrative domains
                            and therefore does not need to include internal system level
                            information of each peering router (e.g. the system name or
                            version information). In order to derive a Loc-RIB to a router,
                            the router name or other system information is needed. The BMP
                            receiver and user are forced to do some type of correlation using
                            what information is available in the peering session (e.g. peering
                            addresses, ASNs, and BGP-ID's). This leads to error prone
                            correlations.
                        </t>
                        <t>
                            The BGP-ID's and session addresses to router correlation
                            requires additional data, such as router inventory. This
                            additional data provides the BMP receiver the ability to map and
                            correlate the BGP-ID's and/or session addresses, but requires the
                            BMP receiver to somehow obtain this data outside of BMP. How this
                            data is obtained and the accuracy of the data directly effects the
                            integrity of the correlation.
                        </t>
                    </list>
                </t>
            </section>
        </section>

        <section title="Terminology">
            <t>
                The key words "MUST", "MUST NOT", "REQUIRED", "SHALL", "SHALL NOT",
                "SHOULD", "SHOULD NOT", "RECOMMENDED", "MAY", and "OPTIONAL" in this
                document are to be interpreted as described in <xref target="RFC2119">RFC 2119</xref>.
            </t>
        </section>

        <section title="Definitions">
            <t>
                <list style="symbols">
                    <t>
                        Adj-RIB-In: As defined in <xref target="RFC4271"/>, "The Adj-RIBs-In contains
                        unprocessed routing information that has been advertised to the
                        local BGP speaker by its peers." This is also referred to as the
                        pre-policy Adj-RIB-In in this document.
                    </t>
                    <t>
                        Adj-RIB-Out: As defined in <xref target="RFC4271"/>, "The Adj-RIBs-Out contains
                        the routes for advertisement to specific peers by means of the
                        local speaker's UPDATE messages."
                    </t>
                    <t>
                        Loc-RIB: As defined in <xref target="RFC4271"/>, "The Loc-RIB contains the routes
                        that have been selected by the local BGP speaker's Decision
                        Process." It is further defined that the routes selected include
                        locally originated and routes from all peers.
                    </t>
                    <t>
                        Pre-Policy Adj-RIB-Out: The result before applying the outbound
                        policy to an Adj-RIB-Out. This normally represents a similar view of the
                        Loc-RIB but may contain additional routes based on BGP peering configuration.
                    </t>
                    <t>
                        Post-Policy Adj-RIB-Out: The result of applying outbound policy to
                        an Adj-RIB-Out. This MUST be what is actually sent to the peer.
                    </t>
                </list>
            </t>
        </section>

        <section title="Per-Peer Header">
            <section title="Peer Type" anchor="PeerType">
                <t>
                    This document defines the following new peer type:

                    <list style="symbols">
                        <t>
                            Peer Type = &IANA_PEER_TYPE_LOC_RIB;: Loc-RIB Instance Peer
                        </t>
                    </list>
                </t>
            </section>

            <section title="Peer Flags" anchor="PeerFlags">
                <t>
                    In <xref target="RFC7854">section 4.2</xref>, the "locally sourced routes" comment under the
                    L flag description is removed.  Locally sourced routes MUST be
                    conveyed using the Loc-RIB instance peer type.

                    <vspace blankLines="1"/>

                    The per-peer header flags for Loc-RIB Instance Peer type are defined
                    as follows:
                </t>
                <figure align="center">
                    <artwork align="center"><![CDATA[
 0 1 2 3 4 5 6 7
+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+
|F|  Reserved   |
+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+
]]></artwork>
                </figure>

                <t>
                    <list style="symbols">
                        <t>
                            The F flag indicates that the Loc-RIB is filtered.  This
                            indicates that the Loc-RIB does not represent the complete routing
                            table.

                            <vspace blankLines="1"/>

                            The remaining bits are reserved for future use. They SHOULD be
                            transmitted as 0 and their values MUST be ignored on receipt.
                        </t>
                    </list>
                </t>
            </section>
        </section>

        <section title="Loc-RIB Monitoring">
            <t>
                Loc-RIB contains all routes from BGP peers as well as any and all
                routes redistributed or otherwise locally originated.  In this
                context, only the BGP instance Loc-RIB is included.  Routes from
                other routing protocols that have not been redistributed, originated by
                or into BGP, or received via Adj-RIB-In are not considered.
            </t>

            <section title="Per-Peer Header">
                <t>
                    All peer messages that include a per-peer header MUST use the
                    following values:

                    <list style="symbols">
                        <t>
                            Peer Type: Set to &IANA_PEER_TYPE_LOC_RIB; to indicate Loc-RIB Instance Peer.
                        </t>
                        <t>
                            Peer Distinguisher: Zero filled if the Loc-RIB represents the
                            global instance.  Otherwise set to the route distinguisher or
                            unique locally defined value of the particular instance the Loc-RIB belongs to.
                        </t>
                        <t>
                            Peer Address: Zero-filled.  Remote peer address is not applicable.
                            The V flag is not applicable with Local-RIB Instance peer type
                            considering addresses are zero-filed.
                        </t>
                        <t>
                            Peer AS: Set to the BGP instance global or default ASN value.
                        </t>
                        <t>
                            Peer BGP ID: Set to the BGP instance global or RD (e.g. VRF)
                            specific router-id.
                        </t>
                    </list>
                </t>

            </section>

            <section title="Peer UP Notification" anchor="PeerUpNotify">
                <t>
                    Peer UP notifications follow <xref target="RFC7854">section 4.10</xref> with the
                    following clarifications:

                    <list style="symbols">
                        <t>
                            Local Address: Zero-filled, local address is not applicable.
                        </t>
                        <t>
                            Local Port: Set to 0, local port is not applicable.
                        </t>
                        <t>
                            Remote Port: Set to 0, remote port is not applicable.
                        </t>
                        <t>
                            Sent OPEN Message: This is a fabricated BGP OPEN message.
                            Capabilities MUST include 4-octet ASN and all necessary
                            capabilities to represent the Loc-RIB route monitoring messages.
                            Only include capabilities if they will be used for Loc-RIB
                            monitoring messages.  For example, if add-paths is enabled for
                            IPv6 and Loc-RIB contains additional paths, the add-paths
                            capability should be included for IPv6.  In the case of add-paths,
                            the capability intent of advertise, receive or both can be ignored
                            since the presence of the capability indicates enough that add-
                            paths will be used for IPv6.
                        </t>
                        <t>
                            Received OPEN Message: Repeat of the same Sent Open Message.  The
                            duplication allows the BMP receiver to use existing parsing.
                        </t>

                    </list>
                </t>

                <section title="Peer UP Information" anchor="PeerUpInfoTlv">
                    <t>
                        The following peer UP information TLV types are added:

                        <list style="symbols">
                            <t>
                                Type = &IANA_PEER_UP_INFO_TLV_TABLE_NAME;: VRF/Table Name.  The Information field contains an
                                ASCII string whose value MUST be equal to the value of the VRF or
                                table name (e.g. RD instance name) being conveyed.  The string size
                                MUST be within the range of 1 to 255 bytes.

                                <vspace blankLines="1"/>

                                The VRF/Table Name TLV is optionally included. For consistency, it
                                is RECOMMENDED that the VRF/Table Name always be included.  The
                                default value of "global" SHOULD be used for the default Loc-RIB
                                instance with a zero-filled distinguisher.
                            </t>
                        </list>
                    </t>
                </section>
            </section>

            <section title="Peer Down Notification">
                <t>
                    Peer down notification SHOULD follow the <xref target="RFC7854">section 4.9</xref>
                    reason 2.
                </t>
            </section>

            <section title="Route Monitoring">
                <t>
                    Route Monitoring messages are used for initial synchronization of
                    the Loc-RIB.  They are also used to convey incremental Loc-RIB
                    changes.

                    <vspace blankLines="1"/>

                    As defined in <xref target="RFC7854">section 4.3</xref>, "Following the common BMP
                    header and per-peer header is a BGP Update PDU."
                </t>

                <section title="ASN Encoding">
                    <t>
                        Loc-RIB route monitor messages MUST use 4-byte ASN encoding as indicated
                        in <xref target="PeerUpNotify">PEER UP sent OPEN message</xref> capability.
                    </t>
                </section>

                <section title="Granularity">
                    <t>
                        State compression and throttling maybe used by a BMP sender implementation
                        to reduce the amount of route monitoring messages that are
                        transmitted to BMP receivers.  With state compression, only the
                        final resultant updates are sent.

                        <vspace blankLines="1"/>

                        For example, prefix 10.0.0.0/8 is updated in the Loc-RIB 5 times
                        within 1 second. State compression of BMP route monitor messages
                        results in only the final change being transmitted. The other 4
                        changes are suppressed because they fall within the compression
                        interval. If no compression was being used, all 5 updates would
                        have been transmitted.

                        <vspace blankLines="1"/>

                        A BMP receiver SHOULD expect that Loc-RIB route monitoring granularity
                        can be different by BMP sender implementation.
                    </t>
                </section>
            </section>

            <section title="Route Mirroring">
                <t>
                    Route mirroring is not applicable to Loc-RIB.
                </t>
            </section>

            <section title="Statistics Report">
                <t>
                    Not all Stat Types are relevant to Loc-RIB.  The Stat Types that
                    are relevant are listed below:

                    <list style="symbols">
                        <t>
                            Stat Type = 8: (64-bit Gauge) Number of routes in Loc-RIB.
                        </t>
                        <t>
                            Stat Type = 10: Number of routes in per-AFI/SAFI Loc-RIB.  The
                            value is structured as: 2-byte AFI, 1-byte SAFI, followed by a 64-
                            bit Gauge.
                        </t>
                    </list>
                </t>
            </section>
        </section>

        <section title="Other Considerations">
            <section title="Loc-RIB Implementation">
                <t>
                    There are several methods to implement Loc-RIB efficiently.  In all
                    methods, the implementation emulates a peer with Peer UP and DOWN
                    messages to convey capabilities as well as Route Monitor messages to
                    convey Loc-RIB.  In this sense, the peer that conveys the Loc-RIB is
                    a local router emulated peer.
                </t>

                <section title="Multiple Loc-RIB Peers">
                    <t>
                        There MUST be multiple emulated peers for each Loc-RIB instance, such
                        as with VRF's. The BMP receiver identifies the Loc-RIB's by the peer
                        header distinguisher and BGP ID.  The BMP receiver uses the VRF/Table
                        Name from the PEER UP information to associate a name to the Loc-RIB.

                        <vspace blankLines="1"/>

                        In some implementations, it might be required to have more than one
                        emulated peer for Loc-RIB to convey different address families for
                        the same Loc-RIB.  In this case, the peer distinguisher and BGP ID
                        should be the same since it represents the same Loc-RIB instance.
                        Each emulated peer instance MUST send a PEER UP with the OPEN message
                        indicating the address family capabilities.  A BMP receiver MUST
                        process these capabilities to know which peer belongs to which
                        address family.
                    </t>
                </section>

                <section title="Filtering Loc-RIB to BMP Receivers">
                    <t>
                        There maybe be use-cases where BMP receivers should only receive
                        specific routes from Loc-RIB. For example, IPv4 unicast routes may
                        include IBGP, EBGP, and IGP but only routes from EBGP should be sent
                        to the BMP receiver.  Alternatively, it may be that only IBGP and
                        EBGP that should be sent and IGP redistributed routes should be
                        excluded.  In these cases where the Loc-RIB is filtered, the F flag
                        is set to 1 to indicate to the BMP receiver that the Loc-RIB is
                        filtered.
                    </t>
                </section>
            </section>
        </section>

        <section title="Security Considerations">
            <t>
                It is not believed that this document adds any additional security
                considerations.
            </t>
        </section>

        <section title="IANA Considerations">
            <t>
                This document requests that IANA assign the following new parameters
                to the <eref
                          target="https://www.iana.org/assignments/bmp-parameters/bmp-parameters.xhtml">
                BMP parameters name space</eref>.
            </t>

            <section title="BMP Peer Type">
                <t>
                    This document defines a new peer type (<xref target="PeerType"/>):

                    <list style="symbols">
                        <t>
                            Peer Type = &IANA_PEER_TYPE_LOC_RIB;: Loc-RIB Instance Peer
                        </t>
                    </list>
                </t>
            </section>

            <section title="BMP Peer Flags">
                <t>
                    This document defines a new flag (<xref target="PeerFlags"/>) and proposes that peer
                    flags are specific to the peer type:

                    <list style="symbols">
                        <t>
                            The F flag indicates that the Loc-RIB is filtered.  This indicates
                            that the Loc-RIB does not represent the complete routing table.
                        </t>
                    </list>
                </t>
            </section>

            <section title="Peer UP Information TLV">
                <t>
                    This document defines the following new BMP PEER UP informational
                    message TLV types (<xref target="PeerUpInfoTlv"/>):

                    <list style="symbols">
                        <t>
                            Type = &IANA_PEER_UP_INFO_TLV_TABLE_NAME;: VRF/Table Name.
                            The Information field contains an ASCII string whose value MUST be equal to the
                            value of the VRF or table name (e.g. RD instance name) being conveyed.
                            The string size MUST be within the range of 1 to 255 bytes.
                        </t>
                    </list>
                </t>
            </section>
        </section>


    </middle>

    <back>

        <references title="Normative References">
            &RFC2119;

            <?rfc include="reference.RFC.4271.xml"?>
        <?rfc include="reference.RFC.7854.xml"?>

        </references>

        <!--<references title="Informative References">-->
            <!--<?rfc include="reference.I-D.draft-evens-grow-bmp-adj-rib-out-01.xml"?>-->
        <!--</references>-->

        <section anchor="Acknowledgements" title="Acknowledgements" numbered="no">
            <t>
                The authors would like to thank John Scudder for his valuable input.
            </t>
        </section>

    </back>
</rfc>
